Brooks, George Additional Papers /4112
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
George Brooks Additional Papers
1945-1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brooks, George W.
/4112
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
7989291
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 30, 2016
Biographical / Historical
George Brooks (July 12, 1908 January 27, 2000) was a professor at Cornell University's School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
A graduate of Yale University (BA, 1930) and Brown University (MA, 1932), Brooks worked for the National Mediation Board, National Labor Relations Board, and the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulfite, and Paper Mill Workers until he joined the ILR School in 1961. Brooks published in the Industrial and Labor Relations Review, Cornell Law Review, Review of Law and Social Change, and Monthly Labor Review.
See the Cornell University Faculty Memorial Statement for Professor George Brooks: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/17900
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4003: ILR School ILR Service Training Course Manuals /4098: George Brooks Additional Papers /4148: George Brooks Additional Papers
Brooks, George
7989291
- ILR Council, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Provost Committee, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sub-Committees subjects, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- sc Faculty, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Research, publications, Library (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Students, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Extension, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Labor Liberal Arts College, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- SUNY, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Field Study, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Source material, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Mission, 1945-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Final Report 12-71, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Text of Report, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Draft, recommendations 9 and 12-71, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Drafts, fall 1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Drafts, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Committee Reactions, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Misc., 1955-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Misc., 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)